[{"answer": "You know, things are certainly moving forward.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "Any sense on where we are after one week in terms of the takings?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "It's disastrous.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Is this a force for good or a forceful continued concern as America moves now to legalizing marijuana?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well I'll tell you.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "What is the difference?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "I think it destroys thousands.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 75, "question": "How many lives, percentage-wise do you think it destroys?", "qSentId": 74}, {"answer": "But what are ...", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "OK?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "And the front lines that I've been on are ones of law enforcement obviously.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Obviously, a pretty damning verdict there from Howard Samuels, from your experience of law enforcement, what do you make of this move today?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "OK, on that very point, are you happy with the steps that Colorado, for example, reporting you have to be 21 or older, you can buy up to an ounce with a license on stores (inaudible) Colorado ID, people from outside Colorado can buy a quarter ounce, users can also share an ounce of cannabis with a friend.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "The challenge is how do we responsibly regulate marijuana as a legal product given the failures in the past?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Are you happy with that criteria?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "... (inaudible) it should not be arrest record for marijuana, but you don't legalize it and mass produce it, just like the ...", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Taking away their job, including that, right?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "Too late.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "And if not, why not?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "Well, you see, I look a little bit -- I've been called all kinds of things.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "How's your skin doing?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "We're not able to disclose where she is.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "You have Jahi back with you, are you able to say where she is?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Because we believe that as long as her heart is still pumping, she's still alive.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 256, "question": "Why do you believe that they're wrong, that there is still hope and she may still be alive?", "qSentId": 255}, {"answer": "Absolutely, she is moving a lot more.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Are you seeing any signs of what you think could be evidence that she is alive?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Well, the situation is sort one in limbo because the coroner on one hand says she is dead.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "Do they have complete legal rights over her body now?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "No, what we wanted to do was have her mother have the ability to make a choice as to whether or not her daughter would stay on or come off of the vent.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "But do you want from a legal point of view to have more physicians examine her to determine whether they agree with the original verdict that she is brain dead?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Should that always be, do you think, a family's choice?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 286, "question": "You feel that strongly, Omari?", "qSentId": 285}, {"answer": "Right now we're just taking it one day at a time.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 297, "question": "How long will you as a family persevere?", "qSentId": 296}, {"answer": "Not so much -- I mean absolutely.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 301, "question": "Are you working on the theory that miracles happen?", "qSentId": 300}, {"answer": "Jahi is a very sweet girl.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "For those who do have meet her, have met her, what kind of girl is she?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "Nothing's changed medically.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 354, "question": "Arthur Caplan, we've discussed this before, has anything changed in your opinion of this case since we last talked about it given that there's now the movement in terms of the apparent legal position?", "qSentId": 353}, {"answer": "You know, I checked this.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "Has anybody to your knowledge recovered after being declared brain dead?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "You know, Piers, I think from a human perspective it's heartbreaking and difficult.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "What do you make of it?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "Because there is -- and frankly, you know, I don't know much about the New Jersey law but when you have a situation when a child is dead, the responsibility is for the hospital and the parents to come to terms and understand that but there is no remedy here.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "Why does it not exist elsewhere?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "You know, I'll answer this way.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 392, "question": "Why should we be stopping this family from being in that position?", "qSentId": 391}, {"answer": "There's another case in Texas which is fascinating on a different level.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "If we left it up to you and me grieving over our families, who's going to say give up?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Well, for me, Texas legislature has no business intruding into this tragedy.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "Now, where do you sit with that, Arthur Caplan?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "It was a story of hope and opportunity in an area that doesn't have too many of them, areas that have, you know, high crime, high poverty, and I met these boys, they weren't waiting for someone to help them, they were doing it on their own.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 438, "question": "We also know that his older brother Johnny is here as well has got into UMass, why did this story touching out with you?", "qSentId": 437}, {"answer": "Yes, that's right.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "OK, George let me start with you because you've been offered a place at Yale, but brilliantly you have made your mind (inaudible) because you're still quite fancy (inaudible), is that right?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Definitely really exciting that we have come such a long way from, you know, poverty, single parent, and it's definitely really exciting for me to be accepted to, you know, Ivy college but as well as for my brother to attend, you know, a college already and, you know, it feels amazing to, you know, be in the right path and...", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 454, "question": "How do you feel about what has happened to you and to your brother?", "qSentId": 453}, {"answer": "I don't know if I can call it the American dream but we're getting closer to that I suppose because I have still yet to graduate from college, although we have been given many privileges of being able to be educated and we're well on our way.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 458, "question": "Do you feel, Johnny, that you are now living perhaps the American dream your parents wanted to live when they came here?", "qSentId": 457}, {"answer": "Well, we'd spoke before and of course Donnie Wahlberg is my (inaudible).", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Tell me about that?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "Well I don't think they -- I don't think they call themselves special.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 472, "question": "Well, what made these boys special enough to be able to make this miraculous achievement which is what many people see it as?", "qSentId": 471}, {"answer": "Find hobbies to do.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 480, "question": "What is your advice to other kids in that area and neighborhoods like that around America for avoiding the pitfalls of crime and violence and so on?", "qSentId": 479}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "George, what do you think?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "They are very capable of being typical teenagers.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 491, "question": "Any play that goes on?", "qSentId": 490}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "This is only the second time you got on a plane in your lives was to come to the studio today, right?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "He would have been very proud of us.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "ORGAN: By the time you got back to your -- where your parents came from in Vietnam, what do you think your father would have made with the fact that you've been offered this place at Yale and you're at UMass?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "He definitely did, because I mean when I was in elementary school he would always check my homework, make sure I was doing well.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "So George, I mean, do you think that he instilled in you the kind of values that you're clearly showing us tonight?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "It's billy_baker.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "What's your Twitter address?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "I mean more so, Emmett, certainly.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "The pair of you have been almost surrogate fathers, haven't you?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Studying chemical engineering.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "What are you doing at UMass?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Chemical engineer.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 536, "question": "ORGAN: What do you want to be?", "qSentId": 535}, {"answer": "Thinking about studying biomedical engineering.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "What about you, what are you going to be?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Journalism.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "What do you want to be?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Maybe.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "You'll be a journalist?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "You know what for just for you, Piers, the temperature is exactly the same in Celsius as it is in Fahrenheit.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Just how cold is it getting out there?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "All the way through until Friday.", "docId": "140106pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "(inaudible) tonight?", "qSentId": 573}]